A Guide to the Alfred E. Cohn papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA132
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1
  - Kahlson, Georg, 1929 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kahn, R.F., 1933 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kandel, I.L., 1935 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Karsner, Howard T., 1929-1930 1934 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kassel, C.Y., 1932 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kast, L., 1935 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Katterfield, L.E., 1933 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Katz, L.N., 1931 1933 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kaufmann, Jacob, 1928 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Keefer, Chester S., 1928 1930 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kelley, Stephen G., 1928 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kendrick, Ruth C., 1935 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kennedy, Foster (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kent, H.W., 1934 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Keppel, F.P., 1933 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kadison, Alexander, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kaempffert, Waldemar (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kaempffert, Waldemar, 1943 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kagan, Solomon R., 1941-1942 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kaiser, Helen, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Karelson, F.E. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kassel, L.H. and C.Y., 1941 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Katz, Louis N., 1943 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Katzki, Herbert (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kaufmann, S., 1943 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kaufman, William, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Katz, L.N., 1941 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kaunitz, Julius, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kelley, Nicholas, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kellogg, Paul, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kelly, John, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kennedy, Edward (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Keppel, F.B., 1940-1943 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kidd, John G., 1944 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kiernan, Frank (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kilgore, Senator H.M. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kimball, Dr. Everett (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - King, William D., 1943-1944 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kirchwey, Freda, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kirps, Joseph, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kleiner, Israel S., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kligler, Israel J., 1944 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Knoll's Bookbindery, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Knopf, Alfred A., 1941 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Koehler, Mrs. Phyllis (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kohn, Jerome L., 1944 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kohn, Lucile, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Koller, Carl, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Komora, Paul O., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Koplik, Lewis Henry, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Korenchevsky, Dr. V. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kotchnig, Dr. W.M. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kramer, Samuel Noah, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Krumbhaar, E.B., 1941-1942 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kubie, Lawrence S., 1941-1943 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kunkel, L.O., 1940 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kurzman, George F. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kuttner (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kula Interior Decorator, 1943 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Keppel, F.P., 1940 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - King, Kathleen C., 1932 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Kingsbury, J.A., 1931 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Kinney, Miss, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Kligler, I.J., 1928-1929 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Knapp, D.R. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Kober Medal, 1930 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Koehler, Phyllis B., 1932 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Koehler, Alfred E., 1928 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Kohut, Mrs. Alexander, 1935 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Kohut, G.A. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Koller, Carl, 1928 1934 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Koller, Lewis R., 1933 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Koppanyi, Theodore (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Kotschnig, W.M., 1935 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Kramer, Benjamin, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Krause, Alan K., 1930 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Krickl, Maurice, 1935 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Krogh, August, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Krogh, Marie, 1929 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Krumbhaar, E.B., 1928-1929 1931 1935 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Kubie, Lawrence S., 1932 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Kugelmass, I. Newton, 1931 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Külbs, Prof., 1929 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Kuntz, Alfred, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Kuttner, Ann G., 1930-1931 1935 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Kiernan, Frank (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kilborn, Robert C., 1937 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kimmel, William, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - King, Sohtsu G., 1937 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kisch, Dr. Bruno, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kissel, Alice, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Klein, Simon R., 1936 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - "The King of Kings", undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kleiner, Israel S., 1936 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Knopf, S.A., 1936 1939 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kohn, Robert D. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Koller, Carl, 1936 1938 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kopetzky, Samuel J., 1939 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Korenchevsky, Dr. V. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kotschnig, Dr. W.M. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kovacs, Richard, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Krauthheimer, Richard, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Krehbiel, Edward, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Krumbhaar, E.B., 1936-1938 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kubie, Lawrence S. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kubie, Lawrence S., 1938 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kuttner, Ann (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Klebs, ARnold, 1932 1934 1936-1939 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Kidd, John, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - King, Frances, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Kingsbury, I.W., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Kirps, Maurice, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Kirchwey, Freda, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Kisch, Bruno (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Krickl, Maurice, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Kubie, Lawrence S., 1946 1951-1953 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Kirps, Maurice, 1943-1945 1947 1953 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Kotschnig, Walter M., 1947 1952 1954 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Kellogg, Paul, 1934-1937 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Kirps, Maurice, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Knapp, John D., 1924 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Koch, Ernst, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Kollarits, Prof. J., 1926 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Kretschmar, A.W., 1926 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Krumbahaar, Edward B., 1926 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Kugelmass, I. Newton, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Kassel, Mrs. L.H., 1946-1948 1950 1952 1953 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Kaul, Mrs. John, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Kenyon Review, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Keesing, S.H., 1951 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Kligler, I.J., 1923-1927, undated (Box 17, Folder 12-13)
  - Laing, G.C. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Ladd, William S., 1937 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Lambert, Samuel W., 1936-1939 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Landsteiner, K., 1937 1939 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Lanza, A.J., 1937 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Levy, F.H., 1937 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Landis, J.M., 1936 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Lape, Esther Everett, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Lasker, Albert D., 1936-1939 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Lasker, Miss Loula D., 1938 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Lawton, George, 1937 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Langley, C.J., 1938 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - LaDue, John S., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lambert, Dr. Robert, 1944 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lambert, Samuel W. and Mrs., 1940-1942 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lamont, Joseph R. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lamport, Dr. Harold (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lamson, Dr. Paul D., 1941 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lancet, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Landauer, Walter, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Landsteiner, Dr. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Langer, Honorable William (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Laquer, Dr. E., 1946 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lasker, Albert D., 1940 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lasker, Mary Woodard (Mrs. Albert D.), 1945 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lawton, George, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lauterbach, Mr. Herbert F., 1945 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lall, Debi, 1925-1926 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Lamb, Brockenbrough, 1923-1924 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Lattin, Dr. Benton, 1923-1924 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Lall, Debi, 1929 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Lamb, Arthur E., 1934 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Lambert, Samuel W., 1933 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Landis, Honorable James, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Landauer, Walter, 1932 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Landt, Dr. Harry (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Langmuir, Alexander D., 1935 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Lapham, Dr. Mary E., 1929 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - L'Art Ancien S.A., 1932 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Lash, George M., 1931 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Lasker, Albert D., 1928 1932 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Lasker, Loula Dr., 1935 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Lathorpe, George H., 1933 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Lancefield, Rebecca, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Lange, Fritz, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Lansing, A.I., 1950 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Lanson, G., 1951 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Lasker, Mrs. Albert D., 1948 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Lavin, G.L., 1951 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Lax, Henry, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Lasker Foundation for Medical Research, 1928-1929 1931-1938 (Box 18, Folder 6-9)
  - Lash, Joseph P., 1941-1942 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Laski, Frida (Mrs. Harold), 1950 1952-1954 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Laski Mathewson, Diana, 1947 1950 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Laski, Harold J. Library Memorial Project, 1950 1952-1953 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Leake, Chauncey D., 1928 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Leathes, J.B., 1934 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Lebowich, Richard J., 1931 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Levy, Flora, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Lee, Frederic S., 1928 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Leech, Clifton B., 1928 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Leeds & Northrup Co., 1930-1931 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Lehman, H.H., 1928 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Leiter, Louis, 1929-1932 1935 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Le Mée, J.M., 1930 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Lemering (?), Claudine, 1934-1935 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Leschke, E., 1931 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Leuba, James H., 1933 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Leuger (?), Reuben, 1939 (?) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Levene, Mrs. P.A., 1928 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Levene, P.A. ("Fedja"), 1930-1934 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Levine, S.A., 1928-1930 1933 1935 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Levine, S.Z., 1928 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Levy, David M., 1931-1934 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Levis, Thomas, 1928 1930 undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Lewis, William, 1931-1935 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Libman, Emanuel, 1929 1934-1935 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Lichtman, S.S., 1932 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Lichty, John A., 1928 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Lieb, Charles C., 1932-1933 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - L, Charles J., 1934 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Liebman, Mrs. Julius, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Linfield, H.S., 1935 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Lingg, Claire (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Lips, Julius, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Lloyd, Wray, 1929-1930 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Lebowitz, Lillian, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Lehmann-Hartleben, Karl, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Leiter, Louis (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Levene, Dr. George (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Levene, P.A. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Levene, P.A., 1937 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Levi, William Grant (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Levine, Samuel A., 1936-1938 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Levy, Dr., 1938 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Levy, Mrs. Irma (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Levy, Robert L., 1936 1938 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Levy, Robert L. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Li, K.C., 1936 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Libman, Emanuel, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Libman, Henry (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Liebman, Walter J., 1939 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Lilienthal, David E., 1939 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Lingg, Claire (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Lisowski, Eunice (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Lisowski, Eunice, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Littell, Robert, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Livingston, Goodhue, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Lewis, William H. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Lewis, William H. Jr., 1936-1941 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Lewis, H.K. and Co., Ltd., 1936-1939 1946-1953 (Box 19, Folder 8-9)
  - Leavitt, M.A. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Lee, Porter E. Jr. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Leikind, Morris C., 1945 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Lerner, Max, 1939-1942 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Lessell, Edw. A., 1942 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Levine, S.A., 1943 1945 1951 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Levy, David, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Levy, D. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Levy, Mrs. Louis S. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Levy, Robert L., 1940-1941 1943 1944-1945 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Levy, Robert L. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Lewin, Bertram D., 1944 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Lewis, Sir Thomas [re], 1945 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Lewis, Wilmarth S., 1941 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Lhamon, Wm. T., 1942 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Libman, E., 1942 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Lieberman, Joshua, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Library Bureau Division, 1943 1950 1953 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Liebman, Charles J. and Mrs., 1940 1943 1948 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Liebman, C.J. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Liebman, Walter H. and Mrs., 1942-1943 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Liebman, Mrs. Walter H. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Lilienthal, David E., 1940-1942 1945 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Lingg, Claire, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Lingg, Claire (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Lim, C.E., 1940 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Lindbergh, Charles A., 1941 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Linsker, Claire, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Lipkin, Mack, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Lippmann, Walter, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Lipnitz, Ida, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Lisowski, Miss, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Listcodes (Federal Security Agency), 1943-1944 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Liu, J. Heng, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Leiter, Louis, 1927 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Leschke, Erich, 1924 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Levene, P.A., 1923 1926 undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Levine, Samuel A., 1923-1925 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Levy, Robert L., 1925-1927 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Levy, Irma B., 1926 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Lewinski-Corwin, E.H., 1925-1926 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Lewis, Frederic T., 1923 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Lewis, W.H., 1926 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Libman, E., 1922-1925 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Liebman, Charles J., 1924 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Lindsay, Samuel McCune, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Lippmann, Walter, 1924 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Littell, Robert, 1923 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Leighton, Alexander H., 1948 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Lerner, Max, 1947 1949 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Lerner, Edna (Mrs. Max), 1950 1953 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Levine, Harry, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Levy, Robert L., 1946-1947 1949 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Lewin, Bertram D., 1946 1948 1953 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Lewis, Wilmarth, 1947-1949 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Lewisohn, Richard, 1951 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Liebman, Mrs. Walter, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Lilienthal, David, 1946-1947 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Lindstedt, Mrs. Diddie, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Livingston, Robert, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Litvak, Anatole, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Lloyd, R. McAllister, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - "What is a Liberal? ", 1949 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Littauer, Lucius N., 1929 1937 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Littauer Foundation, Lucius N., 1945-1947 (Box 20, Folder 5-6)
  - Lieb, John W., 1927 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Love, A.G., 1927 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Loveman, Amy, 1927 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Lowenstein, Oscar, 1926 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Lowenthal, Max, 1927 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Lundsgaard, Prof., 1923 1926 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Lusk, Graham, 1923 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Lange, Fritz, 1927-1932 1934-1935 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Logie, H.B., 1930-1935 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Lowell, P.M., 1929 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Loveman, Amy, 1933-1934 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Lowenstein, Mrs. Melvyn, 1928 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Lowenstein, Oscar, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Lowenstein, Mrs. Oscar, 1932-1933 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Lowenstein, Nina, 1933 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Lowenthal, Dr., 1935 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Lundsgaard, C., 1930 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Lupineck (sic), B., 1932 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Lusk, Graham, 1928-1929 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Lyon, D., 1933 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Lyon, James Alexander, 1934 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Lockie, Alice N., 1941 1943-1944 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Long, Esmond R., 1945 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Lovell, Malcolm R., 1940-1941 1945 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Lovell, Mrs. Walter, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Lowenstein, Mrs. Melvin, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Lowenstein, Nina, 1940-1943 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Lowenthal, John, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Lowenthal, Eleanor (Mrs. Max), 1944 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Lowenthal, Max, 1940-1942 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Locke Steel Chain Company, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Lockhoff, Doris G., 1946 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Lockie, Alice N., 1950 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Long, Mrs. W.H., 1946 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Long, J.C., 1948 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Lord and Taylor, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Loveman, Amy, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Lowenstein, James Gordon, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Lowenthal, David, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Luker, N.G., 1949-1952 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Lupinek, Bernard, 1947 1950 1952 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Lynd, Robert S., 1947 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Lowenthal, Max, 1946 1948 1953 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Lowenthal, Mrs. Max, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Lyons, Louis M., 1946-1947 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Lobenstine, Edwin C., undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Loeb, Robert F., 1936 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Logie, H.B., 1936-1937 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Lorente de No, Dr., 1938 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Loring, Hubert S., 1936 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Loughborough, Grace, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Loveman, Amy (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Lowenstein, Leon and Mrs., 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Lowenstein, Oscar (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Lowenthal, David, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Lulenski, Dr. Chester R., 1939 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Lupinek, B., 1936 1939 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Lockwood, Mrs. Manice de F. (" Aggie"), 1952-1953 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Lorenz, Theodore, 1930-1937 1943 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Manhattan House, 1950-1953 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Magnes, Mrs. Judah L., 1948 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Magnes, Jonathan, 1948-1949 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - May, Herbert and Carrie, 1936-1946 1951 (Box 21, Folder 8-10)
  - Mabbott, Thomas Ollive, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - MacDowell, H.W., 1944 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Mack, Julian w., 1940 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Mackenzie, G.M., 1940 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Macleod, A. Garrard, 1940-1941 1953 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Macmillan Co. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - MacNider, Wm. de B. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Magnes, J.L., 1944 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Malloch, A. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Mandia, Louis, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Mann, Dr., 1940 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Mansbridge, F. Ronald, 1941-1943 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Mansbridge, Georgia, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Maret, Morris, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Marshall, James, 1941 1944 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Martin, Walton, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Martin, C.F., 1941 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Mason, H.H., 1944 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Marvin, H.M. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Master, Arthur, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Master Reporting Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Mautner, Robert, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Magnus, R., 1926 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Mann, Hubert, 1923 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Marshall, E.K. Jr., 1925 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Martin, C.F., 1924 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Marvin, H.M., 1923 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Mason, Max, 1927 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Mack, Julian W., 1928 1930-1931 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - MacKay, Eaton M., 1930-1931 1935 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Mackenzie, Myra, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Magnes, Judah L., 1928-1931 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Mcguire, John, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Mahaim, Ivan, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Makinsky, A. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Mandlebaum, Helen, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Mann, Hubert, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Marcel, Haulet, 1930-1931 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Martin, Franklin H., 1928 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Martin, Thomas A., 1932 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Marvin, H.M., 1928 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Mason, Max, 1929 1933 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Mason, Edward, 1929 1932 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Mason, Howard H., 1933 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Matusoff, Irving, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Matz, Philip B. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - May, Herbert L., 1931 1935 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Maynard, Edwin P. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - MacDermot, H.E. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - MacKay, Ian F.S., 1953 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - MacLatchy, Josephine, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Magnes, Judah L., 1946 1948 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Magnes, Beatrice (Mrs. Judah L.), 1948 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Magnes, Jonathan, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Mallen, Salazar, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Malloch, Archibald, 1946 1949 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Manfred, Ernest F., 1952 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Mansbridge, Ronald, 1946-1947 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Mansfeld, G., 1949-1950 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Maraamorosch, Karl, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Mark Cross Co., 1951 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Martin, Hayes, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Marvin, H.M., 1946 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Masaryk, Institute, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Mason, Howard H., 1951 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Mateja, W.J., 1946 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Mayer, Albert, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Mayer, Leo, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Maynard, E.P. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Mack, Julian W., 1936 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - MacLeod, Colin, 1937-1938 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - MacNider, Wm. de B., 1936-1938 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Magnes, Jonathan, 1936 1938 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Mahler, C.H., 1936 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Maguire, John, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Malloch, A. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Manges, Morris, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Mann, Hubert, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - March of Time (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Martin, F.C. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Marvin, H.M. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Master, A.M. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Matthews, Adelaide A., 1936 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Maynard, Edwin P., 1938 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - MacCallum, W.G., 1924 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - McCann, W.S., 1929 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - McCartney, J.E., 1930 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - McCreery, James and Co., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - McCulloch, Hugh, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Macdonald, Christine, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - McEwen, Currier, 1930 1932 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - McGraw-Hill, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - McGregor, J.H., 1930 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Mcquire, John, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - McInnes, D.A., 1931 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - McIntosh, J.F., 1929 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - McKellor, Harry R., 1924 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - MacLean, Jessie [re], 1934 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Macleod, A. Garrard, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - McMaster, Philip, 1929, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Macmillan, Mrs. E., 1927 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - MacNeal, Ward J., 1932 1935-1936 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - MacNider, Wm. de B., 1931-1932 1934 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - McDonald, James G., 1946 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - McNider, William de B., 1946 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - McBee, Marian (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - McCormick, Myra J., 1938 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - McDaniel, W.B. 2nd, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - McEwen, Currier, 1937-1938 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - McDonald, James G. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - McIntire, W.A., 1938 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Miller, Genevieve, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - MaGee, Marjorie B. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - McCulloch, William P., 1940 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - McEwen, Currier, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - McGeachey, Craig, 1941 1944 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - MacNeal, W.J., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - McMaster, Philip D., 1944 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - McLean, Franklin C. ("Mac"), 1921-1922 1924-1930 1935 (Box 22, Folder 5-9)
  - McLean, Franklin K. (Box 24, Folder 1-7)
  - McLean, Helen Vincent (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - MacLeish, Archibald (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - MacLeish, Ada (Mrs. Archibald) (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Macleod, A. Garrard (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Macy, Jr. Foundation, Josiah (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Malloch, Archibald (Box 23, Folder 5-6)
  - Meakins, J.C. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - The Medical Clinic of North America Medical education — requirements for career (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Medical Society of the State of New York (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Melicow, Dr. M.M. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Mendel, Lafayette B. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Medical Society of the County of New York (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Mendel, Bruno (?) (Box 23, Folder 7)